const  Feild = [
    {
      question: "What type of system is NetSuite?",
      options: ["CMS", "ERP", "CRM", "Project Management"],
      answer: "ERP",
      category: 'NetSuite'
    },
    {
      question: "Which company owns NetSuite?",
      options: ["Microsoft", "Oracle", "Salesforce", "SAP"],
      answer: "Oracle",
      category: 'NetSuite'

    },
    {
      question: "Which feature allows users to create custom fields, records, and forms?",
      options: ["Advanced Analytics", "Customization Center", "SuiteBuilder", "SuiteScript"],
      answer: "SuiteBuilder",
      category: 'NetSuite'

    },
    {
      question: "What is a Saved Search?",
      options: [
        "A script for custom calculations",
        "A feature for saving financial reports",
        "A tool for creating reusable reports",
        "A way to save global search history",
      ],
      answer: "A tool for creating reusable reports",
      category: 'NetSuite'
    },
    {
      category: "Salesforce",
      question: "What is Salesforce primarily used for?",
      options: [
        "Customer Relationship Management (CRM)",
        "Video Editing",
        "Web Hosting",
        "Operating System Development"
      ],
      answer: "Customer Relationship Management (CRM)"
    },
    {
      category: "Salesforce",
      question: "Which programming language is used to customize Salesforce?",
      options: [
        "Java",
        "Apex",
        "Python",
        "Ruby"
      ],
      answer: "Apex"
    },
    {
      category: "Salesforce",
      question: "What is a key feature of Salesforce that allows automation?",
      options: [
        "Workflows",
        "Lightning Components",
        "AppExchange",
        "Reports"
      ],
      answer: "Workflows"
    },
    {
      category: "Salesforce",
      question: "What is the name of Salesforce's mobile app?",
      options: [
        "Salesforce Anywhere",
        "Salesforce Connect",
        "Salesforce Mobile",
        "Salesforce One"
      ],
      answer: "Salesforce One"
    },
    {
      category: "HubSpot",
      question: "What is HubSpot primarily used for?",
      options: [
        " Content Management",
        " Customer Relationship Management (CRM)",
        " Email Marketing",
        " Web Development"
      ],
      answer: "Customer Relationship Management (CRM)"
    },
    {
      category: "HubSpot",
      question: "Which of the following is a tool offered by HubSpot?",
      options: [
        " Marketing Hub",
        " Adobe Photoshop",
        " Google Analytics",
        " Slack"
      ],
      answer: "Marketing Hub"
    },
    {
      category: "HubSpot",
      question: "Which type of businesses typically use HubSpot?",
      options: [
        " Small to Medium Businesses",
        " Large Corporations Only",
        " Freelancers and Consultants",
        " Government Agencies"
      ],
      answer: "Small to Medium Businesses"
    },
    {
      category: "HubSpot",
      question: "What feature is a part of HubSpot's CRM platform?",
      options: [
        " Content Creation",
        " Lead and Contact Management",
        " Video Editing",
        " Social Media Management"
      ],
      answer: "Lead and Contact Management"
    },
    {
      category: "Slack",
      question: "What is Slack primarily used for?",
      options: [
        "File Sharing",
        "Team Communication and Collaboration",
        "Email Marketing",
        "Social Media Management"
      ],
      answer: "Team Communication and Collaboration"
    },
    {
      category: "Slack",
      question: "Which feature does Slack offer to organize conversations?",
      options: [
        "Channels",
        "Social Media Feeds",
        "Email Lists",
        "Newsletters"
      ],
      answer: "Channels"
    },
    {
      category: "Slack",
      question: "What can users integrate with Slack?",
      options: [
        "GitHub",
        "Salesforce",
        "Google Drive",
        "All of the Above"
      ],
      answer: "All of the Above"
    },
    {
      category: "Slack",
      question: "Which of the following is NOT a Slack feature?",
      options: [
        "Direct Messaging",
        "Group Video Calls",
        "Task Management",
        "Calendar Integration"
      ],
      answer: "Task Management"
    },
    {
      category: "OpenAI",
      question: "What is OpenAI primarily focused on?",
      options: [
        "Building robots",
        "Developing Artificial General Intelligence (AGI)",
        "Creating video games",
        "Developing virtual reality"
      ],
      answer: "Developing Artificial General Intelligence (AGI)"
    },
    {
      category: "OpenAI",
      question: "Which of the following is a product of OpenAI?",
      options: [
        "GPT-3",
        "Microsoft Word",
        "Google Assistant",
        "Alexa"
      ],
      answer: "GPT-3"
    },
    {
      category: "OpenAI",
      question: "What is the primary goal of OpenAI?",
      options: [
        "To create AI for games",
        "To ensure that artificial intelligence benefits humanity",
        "To automate social media",
        "To develop AI for healthcare only"
      ],
      answer: "To ensure that artificial intelligence benefits humanity"
    },
    {
      category: "OpenAI",
      question: "Which of the following is a key feature of GPT-3?",
      options: [
        "It generates human-like text based on prompts",
        "It is a video editing tool",
        "It is a hardware device",
        "It only processes images"
      ],
      answer: "It generates human-like text based on prompts"
    },
    {
      category: "Zendesk",
      question: "What is Zendesk best known for?",
      options: [
        "E-commerce tools",
        "Customer Service and Support Software",
        "Content Management System",
        "Social Media Management"
      ],
      answer: "Customer Service and Support Software"
    },
    {
      category: "Zendesk",
      question: "Which of the following can you use Zendesk for?",
      options: [
        "Handling customer support tickets",
        "Building websites",
        "Managing social media accounts",
        "Designing graphic content"
      ],
      answer: "Handling customer support tickets"
    },
    {
      category: "Zendesk",
      question: "Which feature does Zendesk provide to help with customer interactions?",
      options: [
        "Knowledge Base",
        "File Storage",
        "Video Conferencing",
        "Marketing Automation"
      ],
      answer: "Knowledge Base"
    },
    {
      category: "Zendesk",
      question: "What type of businesses typically use Zendesk?",
      options: [
        "E-commerce and customer support teams",
        "Video game companies",
        "Health organizations",
        "Educational institutions"
      ],
      answer: "E-commerce and customer support teams"
    },
    {
      category: "Indian History",
      question: "Who was the first emperor of the Maurya Dynasty?",
      options: [
        "Chandragupta Maurya",
        "Ashoka the Great",
        "Bindusara",
        "Bimbisara"
      ],
      answer: "Chandragupta Maurya"
    },
    {
      category: "Indian History",
      question: "Which Indian leader is known for his role in the Non-Cooperation Movement of 1920?",
      options: [
        "Jawaharlal Nehru",
        "Mahatma Gandhi",
        "Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel",
        "Subhas Chandra Bose"
      ],
      answer: "Mahatma Gandhi"
    },
    {
      category: "Indian History",
      question: "Who was the founder of the Mughal Empire in India?",
      options: [
        "Akbar",
        "Babur",
        "Shah Jahan",
        "Aurangzeb"
      ],
      answer: "Babur"
    },
    {
      category: "Indian History",
      question: "What was the name of the famous battle where Prithviraj Chauhan was defeated by Muhammad Ghori?",
      options: [
        "Battle of Panipat",
        "Battle of Tarain",
        "Battle of Plassey",
        "Battle of Haldighati"
      ],
      answer: "Battle of Tarain"
    },
    {
      category: "Indian Economy",
      question: "Which is the largest sector of India's economy?",
      options: [
        "Agriculture",
        "Manufacturing",
        "Services",
        "Construction"
      ],
      answer: "Services"
    },
    {
      category: "Indian Economy",
      question: "Which of the following is the main source of income for the Government of India?",
      options: [
        "Direct Taxes",
        "Export Revenues",
        "Foreign Aid",
        "Tourism"
      ],
      answer: "Direct Taxes"
    },
    {
      category: "Indian Economy",
      question: "What is the official currency of India?",
      options: [
        "Dollar",
        "Rupee",
        "Pound",
        "Yen"
      ],
      answer: "Rupee"
    },
    {
      category: "Indian Economy",
      question: "Which institution regulates the monetary policy of India?",
      options: [
        "Reserve Bank of India",
        "Indian Finance Ministry",
        "Securities and Exchange Board of India",
        "World Bank"
      ],
      answer: "Reserve Bank of India"
    },
    {
      category: "Geography",
      question: "What is the capital of India?",
      options: [
        "Mumbai",
        "Kolkata",
        "New Delhi",
        "Chennai"
      ],
      answer: "New Delhi"
    },
    {
      category: "Geography",
      question: "Which is the longest river in India?",
      options: [
        "Ganges",
        "Godavari",
        "Yamuna",
        "Indus"
      ],
      answer: "Ganges"
    },
    {
      category: "Geography",
      question: "Which state is known as the 'Land of the Rising Sun' in India?",
      options: [
        "Arunachal Pradesh",
        "Nagaland",
        "Sikkim",
        "Himachal Pradesh"
      ],
      answer: "Arunachal Pradesh"
    },
    {
      category: "Geography",
      question: "What is the highest peak in India?",
      options: [
        "Kangchenjunga",
        "Mount Everest",
        "Nanda Devi",
        "Makalu"
      ],
      answer: "Kangchenjunga"
    },
    {
      category: "Indian Politics",
      question: "Who was the first Prime Minister of India?",
      options: [
        "Jawaharlal Nehru",
        "Indira Gandhi",
        "Rajiv Gandhi",
        "Lal Bahadur Shastri"
      ],
      answer: "Jawaharlal Nehru"
    },
    {
      category: "Indian Politics",
      question: "Which political party was founded by Dr. B.R. Ambedkar?",
      options: [
        "Indian National Congress",
        "Bharatiya Janata Party",
        "Dalit Panther Party",
        "Republican Party of India"
      ],
      answer: "Republican Party of India"
    },
    {
      category: "Indian Politics",
      question: "Which article of the Indian Constitution gives the right to equality?",
      options: [
        "Article 15",
        "Article 17",
        "Article 21",
        "Article 14"
      ],
      answer: "Article 14"
    },
    {
      category: "Indian Politics",
      question: "Who is the head of the Indian state?",
      options: [
        "Prime Minister",
        "President",
        "Vice President",
        "Chief Justice of India"
      ],
      answer: "President"
    },
    {
      category: "Budget and Taxation",
      question: "What is the primary source of revenue for the Indian government?",
      options: [
        "Taxes",
        "Loans from International Bodies",
        "Sale of Government Bonds",
        "Private Investments"
      ],
      answer: "Taxes"
    },
    {
      category: "Budget and Taxation",
      question: "Which tax is levied on goods and services in India?",
      options: [
        "Goods and Services Tax (GST)",
        "Income Tax",
        "Wealth Tax",
        "Customs Duty"
      ],
      answer: "Goods and Services Tax (GST)"
    },
    {
      category: "Budget and Taxation",
      question: "Which Indian department is responsible for managing national finances?",
      options: [
        "Ministry of Finance",
        "Reserve Bank of India",
        "Securities and Exchange Board of India",
        "Income Tax Department"
      ],
      answer: "Ministry of Finance"
    },
    {
      category: "Budget and Taxation",
      question: "What is the fiscal year for India?",
      options: [
        "January-December",
        "April-March",
        "June-May",
        "October-September"
      ],
      answer: "April-March"
    },
    {
      category: "Space",
      question: "Which was the first satellite launched by India?",
      options: [
        "INSAT-1A",
        "Aryabhata",
        "Chandrayaan-1",
        "Mangalyaan"
      ],
      answer: "Aryabhata"
    },
    {
      category: "Space",
      question: "Which Indian organization is responsible for space research and satellite launches?",
      options: [
        "ISRO",
        "NASA",
        "ESA",
        "JAXA"
      ],
      answer: "ISRO"
    },
    {
      category: "Space",
      question: "What is the name of India's Mars Orbiter Mission?",
      options: [
        "Mangalyaan",
        "Chandrayaan",
        "Astrosat",
        "Gaganyaan"
      ],
      answer: "Mangalyaan"
    },
    {
      category: "Space",
      question: "Who was the first Indian to travel into space?",
      options: [
        "Rakesh Sharma",
        "Kalpana Chawla",
        "Sunita Williams",
        "Vikram Sarabhai"
      ],
      answer: "Rakesh Sharma"
    },
    {
      category: "C",
      question: "What is the size of an int variable in C?",
      options: [
        "1 bytes",
        "4 bytes",
        "8 bytes",
        "16 bytes"
      ],
      answer: "4 bytes"
    },
    {
      category: "C",
      question: "Which function is used to allocate memory dynamically in C?",
      options: [
        "malloc()",
        "calloc()",
        "realloc()",
        "free()"
      ],
      answer: "malloc()"
    },
    {
      category: "C",
      question: "What is the purpose of the 'break' statement in C?",
      options: [
        "To terminate a loop",
        "To pause a loop",
        "To start a loop",
        "To call a function"
      ],
      answer: "To terminate a loop"
    },
    {
      category: "C",
      question: "Which of the following is NOT a valid data type in C?",
      options: [
        "int",
        "char",
        "boolean",
        "float"
      ],
      answer: "boolean"
    },
    {
      category: "C++",
      question: "Which of the following is a feature of Object-Oriented Programming in C++?",
      options: [
        "Encapsulation",
        "Inheritance",
        "Polymorphism",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      answer: "All of the above"
    },
    {
      category: "C++",
      question: "Which of the following is used to define a class in C++?",
      options: [
        "class ClassName {}",
        "object ClassName {}",
        "def ClassName {}",
        "struct ClassName {}"
      ],
      answer: "class ClassName {}"
    },
    {
      category: "C++",
      question: "What does the 'public' keyword represent in a C++ class?",
      options: [
        "Private access modifier",
        "Protected access modifier",
        "Public access modifier",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      answer: "Public access modifier"
    },
    {
      category: "C++",
      question: "Which operator is used to access members of a class in C++?",
      options: [
        ".",
        "->",
        "&",
        "*"
      ],
      answer: "."
    },
    {
      category: "JavaScript",
      question: "What is the correct syntax to print a message in the console?",
      options: [
        "print('Hello World')",
        "console.log('Hello World')",
        "echo('Hello World')",
        "printf('Hello World')"
      ],
      answer: "console.log('Hello World')"
    },
    {
      category: "JavaScript",
      question: "Which company developed JavaScript?",
      options: [
        "Microsoft",
        "Apple",
        "Netscape",
        "Oracle"
      ],
      answer: "Netscape"
    },
    {
      category: "JavaScript",
      question: "What is the result of 2 + '2' in JavaScript?",
      options: [
        "22",
        "4",
        "Error",
        "NaN"
      ],
      answer: "22"
    },
    {
      category: "JavaScript",
      question: "Which method is used to add a new element at the end of an array in JavaScript?",
      options: [
        "append()",
        "push()",
        "insert()",
        "add()"
      ],
      answer: "push()"
    },
    {
      category: "Java",
      question: "What is the default value of a boolean variable in Java?",
      options: [
        "true",
        "false",
        "null",
        "0"
      ],
      answer: "false"
    },
    {
      category: "Java",
      question: "Which of the following is NOT a primitive data type in Java?",
      options: [
        "int",
        "float",
        "String",
        "boolean"
      ],
      answer: "String"
    },
    {
      category: "Java",
      question: "Which method is used to start a thread in Java?",
      options: [
        "start()",
        "run()",
        "execute()",
        "begin()"
      ],
      answer: "start()"
    },
    {
      category: "Java",
      question: "What is the correct way to declare a variable in Java?",
      options: [
        "int 1a;",
        "int a;",
        "int a = 5;",
        "int = a 5;"
      ],
      answer: "int a = 5;"
    },
    {
      category: "Python",
      question: "Which of the following is used to define a function in Python?",
      options: [
        "def function_name():",
        "function function_name():",
        "func function_name():",
        "create function_name():"
      ],
      answer: "def function_name():"
    },
    {
      category: "Python",
      question: "What is the output of the following Python code: print(2 + 3 * 4)?",
      options: [
        "14",
        "20",
        "26",
        "10"
      ],
      answer: "14"
    },
    {
      category: "Python",
      question: "Which method is used to remove whitespace from the beginning and end of a string in Python?",
      options: [
        "strip()",
        "trim()",
        "cut()",
        "remove()"
      ],
      answer: "strip()"
    },
    {
      category: "Python",
      question: "Which of the following is the correct way to write a list in Python?",
      options: [
        "[1, 2, 3, 4]",
        "(1, 2, 3, 4)",
        "{1, 2, 3, 4}",
        "<1, 2, 3, 4>"
      ],
      answer: "[1, 2, 3, 4]"
    },
    {
      category: "React",
      question: "What is React primarily used for?",
      options: [
        "Building mobile apps",
        "Building user interfaces",
        "Building databases",
        "Building web servers"
      ],
      answer: "Building user interfaces"
    },
    {
      category: "React",
      question: "Which function is used to create a component in React?",
      options: [
        "React.createElement()",
        "createComponent()",
        "function Component()",
        "React.Component()"
      ],
      answer: "React.createElement()"
    },
    {
      category: "React",
      question: "What is JSX in React?",
      options: [
        "A JavaScript syntax extension that allows HTML-like code in JavaScript",
        "A new programming language",
        "A tool for styling components",
        "A React library"
      ],
      answer: "A JavaScript syntax extension that allows HTML-like code in JavaScript"
    },
    {
      category: "React",
      question: "Which method is used to update the state in React?",
      options: [
        "setState()",
        "updateState()",
        "changeState()",
        "setStateValue()"
      ],
      answer: "setState()"
    },
    {
      category: "Algebra",
      question: "What is the solution to the equation 2x + 3 = 11?",
      options: [
        "x = 4",
        "x = 5",
        "x = 2",
        "x = 3"
      ],
      answer: "x = 4"
    },
    {
      category: "Algebra",
      question: "What is the value of 'x' in the equation 3x - 7 = 5x + 1?",
      options: [
        "x = -4",
        "x = 6",
        "x = 4",
        "x = -2"
      ],
      answer: "x = -4"
    },
    {
      category: "Algebra",
      question: "Which of the following is the expanded form of (x + 2)(x - 3)?",
      options: [
        "x^2 - x - 6",
        "x^2 - x + 6",
        "x^2 - 5x - 6",
        "x^2 - 5x + 6"
      ],
      answer: "x^2 - 5x - 6"
    },
    {
      category: "Algebra",
      question: "What is the quadratic formula used to solve ax^2 + bx + c = 0?",
      options: [
        "x = (-b ± √(b^2 - 4ac)) / 2a",
        "x = (-b ± √(b^2 + 4ac)) / 2a",
        "x = (-b ± √(b^2 - ac)) / a",
        "x = (-b ± √(a^2 - bc)) / 2a"
      ],
      answer: "x = (-b ± √(b^2 - 4ac)) / 2a"
    },
    {
      category: "Geometry",
      question: "What is the area of a triangle with a base of 5 units and height of 6 units?",
      options: [
        "15 square units",
        "10 square units",
        "12 square units",
        "30 square units"
      ],
      answer: "15 square units"
    },
    {
      category: "Geometry",
      question: "What is the sum of the interior angles of a triangle?",
      options: [
        "180°",
        "360°",
        "90°",
        "270°"
      ],
      answer: "180°"
    },
    {
      category: "Geometry",
      question: "What is the volume of a cube with side length 4 units?",
      options: [
        "16 cubic units",
        "64 cubic units",
        "48 cubic units",
        "32 cubic units"
      ],
      answer: "64 cubic units"
    },
    {
      category: "Geometry",
      question: "What is the circumference of a circle with a radius of 7 units? (Use π = 3.14)",
      options: [
        "21.98 units",
        "14 units",
        "49 units",
        "44.02 units"
      ],
      answer: "43.96 units"
    },
    {
      category: "Arithmetic",
      question: "What is 25% of 200?",
      options: [
        "50",
        "75",
        "100",
        "25"
      ],
      answer: "50"
    },
    {
      category: "Arithmetic",
      question: "What is the sum of 123 + 456?",
      options: [
        "579",
        "589",
        "599",
        "600"
      ],
      answer: "579"
    },
    {
      category: "Arithmetic",
      question: "If you subtract 15 from 50, what is the result?",
      options: [
        "35",
        "45",
        "50",
        "25"
      ],
      answer: "35"
    },
    {
      category: "Arithmetic",
      question: "What is the product of 12 and 9?",
      options: [
        "108",
        "100",
        "110",
        "120"
      ],
      answer: "108"
    },
    {
      category: "Logical Reasoning",
      question: "If all roses are flowers and some flowers fade quickly, can it be concluded that some roses fade quickly?",
      options: [
        "Yes",
        "No",
        "Cannot be determined",
        "Always"
      ],
      answer: "Cannot be determined"
    },
    {
      category: "Logical Reasoning",
      question: "If two pencils are put in a box, and one pencil is taken out, how many pencils remain in the box?",
      options: [
        "1",
        "2",
        "0",
        "3"
      ],
      answer: "1"
    },
    {
      category: "Logical Reasoning",
      question: "Which of the following is the odd one out?",
      options: [
        "Dog",
        "Lion",
        "Tiger",
        "Owl"
      ],
      answer: "Owl"
    },
    {
      category: "Logical Reasoning",
      question: "If all humans are mammals, and John is a human, is John a mammal?",
      options: [
        "Yes",
        "No",
        "Cannot be determined",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      answer: "Yes"
    },
    {
      category: "Trigonometry",
      question: "What is the sine of 30°?",
      options: [
        "1/2",
        "√3/2",
        "√2/2",
        "1"
      ],
      answer: "1/2"
    },
    {
      category: "Trigonometry",
      question: "What is the value of cos(90°)?",
      options: [
        "1",
        "0",
        "-1",
        "undefined"
      ],
      answer: "0"
    },
    {
      category: "Trigonometry",
      question: "What is the tan(45°)?",
      options: [
        "1",
        "0",
        "√3",
        "undefined"
      ],
      answer: "1"
    },
    {
      category: "Trigonometry",
      question: "What is the Pythagorean identity in trigonometry?",
      options: [
        "sin²θ + cos²θ = 1",
        "tan²θ + sec²θ = 1",
        "sin²θ + tan²θ = 1",
        "cos²θ + sec²θ = 1"
      ],
      answer: "sin²θ + cos²θ = 1"
    },
    {
      category: "Cricket",
      question: "Who holds the record for the most runs in a single ODI match?",
      options: [
        "Sachin Tendulkar",
        "Rohit Sharma",
        "Virat Kohli",
        "Ricky Ponting"
      ],
      answer: "Rohit Sharma"
    },
    {
      category: "Cricket",
      question: "What is the maximum number of overs in a standard One Day International (ODI) match?",
      options: [
        "10",
        "20",
        "30",
        "50"
      ],
      answer: "50"
    },
    {
      category: "Cricket",
      question: "Who is the captain of the Indian national cricket team in limited-overs formats (ODI and TEST)?",
      options: [
        "Virat Kohli",
        "MS Dhoni",
        "Rohit Sharma",
        "Sourav Ganguly"
      ],
      answer: "Rohit Sharma"
    },
    {
      category: "Cricket",
      question: "What is the highest individual score in a T20I match?",
      options: [
        "122",
        "118",
        "156",
        "175"
      ],
      answer: "175"
    },
    {
      category: "Football",
      question: "Which country won the 2018 FIFA World Cup?",
      options: [
        "Brazil",
        "Germany",
        "France",
        "Argentina"
      ],
      answer: "France"
    },
    {
      category: "Football",
      question: "Who is known as the 'King of Football'?",
      options: [
        "Lionel Messi",
        "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        "Pele",
        "Diego Maradona"
      ],
      answer: "Pele"
    },
    {
      category: "Football",
      question: "Which club does Cristiano Ronaldo currently play for (as of 2024)?",
      options: [
        "Real Madrid",
        "Manchester United",
        "Juventus",
        "Al Nassr"
      ],
      answer: "Al Nassr"
    },
    {
      category: "Football",
      question: "Which player has won the most Ballon d'Or awards?",
      options: [
        "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        "Lionel Messi",
        "Michel Platini",
        "Zinedine Zidane"
      ],
      answer: "Lionel Messi"
    },
    {
      category: "Hockey",
      question: "Which country won the 2020 Men's Field Hockey Olympic Gold Medal?",
      options: [
        "India",
        "Germany",
        "Australia",
        "Belgium"
      ],
      answer: "Belgium"
    },
    {
      category: "Hockey",
      question: "Who is known as the 'Wizard of Hockey'?",
      options: [
        "Dhyan Chand",
        "Sardar Singh",
        "Balbir Singh",
        "Manpreet Singh"
      ],
      answer: "Dhyan Chand"
    },
    {
      category: "Hockey",
      question: "How many players are on the field for each team in a standard hockey match?",
      options: [
        "8",
        "10",
        "11",
        "7"
      ],
      answer: "11"
    },
    {
      category: "Hockey",
      question: "Which country is considered the birthplace of ice hockey?",
      options: [
        "Canada",
        "USA",
        "Russia",
        "Sweden"
      ],
      answer: "Canada"
    },
    {
      category: "Volleyball",
      question: "How many players are on a team in a standard volleyball match?",
      options: [
        "4",
        "6",
        "7",
        "5"
      ],
      answer: "6"
    },
    {
      category: "Volleyball",
      question: "What is the maximum number of hits allowed for a team before the ball must be sent over the net?",
      options: [
        "1",
        "2",
        "3",
        "4"
      ],
      answer: "3"
    },
    {
      category: "Volleyball",
      question: "Which country won the 2020 Olympic Gold Medal in Men's Volleyball?",
      options: [
        "Brazil",
        "USA",
        "Russia",
        "France"
      ],
      answer: "France"
    },
    {
      category: "Volleyball",
      question: "What is the term for the move where a player jumps to block the opponent's attack?",
      options: [
        "Dig",
        "Spike",
        "Block",
        "Serve"
      ],
      answer: "Block"
    },
    {
      category: "Basketball",
      question: "Which player holds the record for the most points scored in a single NBA game?",
      options: [
        "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
        "Michael Jordan",
        "LeBron James",
        "Wilt Chamberlain"
      ],
      answer: "Wilt Chamberlain"
    },
    {
      category: "Basketball",
      question: "Which NBA team has won the most championships?",
      options: [
        "Los Angeles Lakers",
        "Boston Celtics",
        "Chicago Bulls",
        "Golden State Warriors"
      ],
      answer: "Boston Celtics"
    },
    {
      category: "Basketball",
      question: "Who is known as 'The King' of basketball?",
      options: [
        "Michael Jordan",
        "Kobe Bryant",
        "LeBron James",
        "Shaquille O'Neal"
      ],
      answer: "LeBron James"
    },
    {
      category: "Basketball",
      question: "What is the maximum number of points a player can score in a single possession (without fouls)?",
      options: [
        "2",
        "3",
        "4",
        "5"
      ],
      answer: "3"
    },
    {
      category: "Tennis",
      question: "Which tennis player has won the most Grand Slam singles titles?",
      options: [
        "Roger Federer",
        "Rafael Nadal",
        "Novak Djokovic",
        "Pete Sampras"
      ],
      answer: "Rafael Nadal"
    },
    {
      category: "Tennis",
      question: "Which country is the birthplace of tennis?",
      options: [
        "USA",
        "England",
        "France",
        "Australia"
      ],
      answer: "England"
    },
    {
      category: "Tennis",
      question: "Who won the Wimbledon men's singles title in 2023?",
      options: [
        "Roger Federer",
        "Novak Djokovic",
        "Rafael Nadal",
        "Carlos Alcaraz"
      ],
      answer: "Novak Djokovic"
    },
    {
      category: "Tennis",
      question: "What is the term for scoring zero points in tennis?",
      options: [
        "Love",
        "Fault",
        "Ace",
        "Deuce"
      ],
      answer: "Love"
    },
    {
      category: "Action",
      question: "Which Indian movie features the character 'Kabir' played by Hrithik Roshan?",
      options: [
        "War",
        "Bang Bang!",
        "Dhoom 3",
        "Krrish 3"
      ],
      answer: "War"
    },
    {
      category: "Action",
      question: "In which movie did Akshay Kumar play the role of a police officer named Veer Sooryavanshi?",
      options: [
        "Sooryavanshi",
        "Khatta Meetha",
        "Hera Pheri",
        "Khiladi 786"
      ],
      answer: "Sooryavanshi"
    },
    {
      category: "Action",
      question: "Which action movie is based on the battle between two brothers in a fictional kingdom, starring Salman Khan?",
      options: [
        "Bajrangi Bhaijaan",
        "Kick",
        "Radhe",
        "Tubelight"
      ],
      answer: "Radhe"
    },
    {
      category: "Action",
      question: "Which film features a revenge saga starring Amitabh Bachchan as a character named Vijay?",
      options: [
        "Zanjeer",
        "Sholay",
        "Don",
        "Agneepath"
      ],
      answer: "Agneepath"
    },
    {
      category: "Comedy",
      question: "Which film is known for the iconic character 'Chupke Chupke' starring Dharmendra, Sharmila Tagore, and Amitabh Bachchan?",
      options: [
        "Chupke Chupke",
        "Hera Pheri",
        "Andaz Apna Apna",
        "Bheja Fry"
      ],
      answer: "Chupke Chupke"
    },
    {
      category: "Comedy",
      question: "In which comedy film does Akshay Kumar play the role of a man trying to find a woman for his sister's marriage?",
      options: [
        "Dhadkan",
        "Mujhse Shaadi Karogi",
        "Phir Hera Pheri",
        "Housefull"
      ],
      answer: "Mujhse Shaadi Karogi"
    },
    {
      category: "Comedy",
      question: "Which movie features a comedy duo named Amar and Prem played by Salman Khan and Akshay Kumar?",
      options: [
        "Baaghi",
        "Andaz Apna Apna",
        "Partner",
        "No Entry"
      ],
      answer: "Andaz Apna Apna"
    },
    {
      category: "Comedy",
      question: "In which film does Rajpal Yadav play a hilarious character named 'Lallan'?",
      options: [
        "Masti",
        "Bhool Bhulaiyaa",
        "Hera Pheri",
        "Khatta Meetha"
      ],
      answer: "Masti"
    },
    {
      category: "Drama",
      question: "Which movie stars Shah Rukh Khan as a man who befriends a woman with cancer in 'Kal Ho Naa Ho'?",
      options: [
        "Kabhi Alvida Naa Kehna",
        "Dilwale Dulhania Le Jayenge",
        "Kal Ho Naa Ho",
        "Om Shanti Om"
      ],
      answer: "Kal Ho Naa Ho"
    },
    {
      category: "Drama",
      question: "Which drama movie is based on the life of a farmer, played by Amitabh Bachchan, fighting for justice?",
      options: [
        "Satyagraha",
        "Sholay",
        "Paa",
        "Baghban"
      ],
      answer: "Baghban"
    },
    {
      category: "Drama",
      question: "Which film features Aamir Khan as an underdog wrestler in the movie 'Dangal'?",
      options: [
        "3 Idiots",
        "PK",
        "Dangal",
        "Lagaan"
      ],
      answer: "Dangal"
    },
    {
      category: "Drama",
      question: "Which movie features Kajol as a woman who goes to great lengths to fulfill her late husband's wish in 'Kabhi Khushi Kabhie Gham'?",
      options: [
        "Kabhi Alvida Naa Kehna",
        "Dilwale Dulhania Le Jayenge",
        "Kabhi Khushi Kabhie Gham",
        "Pardes"
      ],
      answer: "Kabhi Khushi Kabhie Gham"
    },
    {
      category: "Horror",
      question: "Which movie features a supernatural story where a spirit haunts a family, starring Rajkummar Rao?",
      options: [
        "Stree",
        "Bhoot",
        "Raaz",
        "Bhool Bhulaiyaa"
      ],
      answer: "Stree"
    },
    {
      category: "Horror",
      question: "Which movie is based on a haunted house, featuring the character of 'Aarti' played by Rani Mukerji?",
      options: [
        "Bhootnath",
        "Raaz",
        "Mahal",
        "Aatma"
      ],
      answer: "Raaz"
    },
    {
      category: "Horror",
      question: "In which film does Emraan Hashmi play the lead role in a thriller about paranormal activities?",
      options: [
        "Raaz: The Mystery Continues",
        "Haunted 3D",
        "Bhoot",
        "Aatma"
      ],
      answer: "Raaz: The Mystery Continues"
    },
    {
      category: "Horror",
      question: "Which horror-comedy movie has the iconic song 'Aayi Teri Yaad'?",
      options: [
        "Murder",
        "Bhootnath",
        "Bhool Bhulaiyaa",
        "Haunted 3D"
      ],
      answer: "Bhool Bhulaiyaa"
    },
    {
      category: "Romance",
      question: "In which film does Shah Rukh Khan play a character who falls in love with a woman in Switzerland?",
      options: [
        "Dilwale Dulhania Le Jayenge",
        "Kabhi Khushi Kabhie Gham",
        "Dil Se",
        "Jab Tak Hai Jaan"
      ],
      answer: "Dilwale Dulhania Le Jayenge"
    },
    {
      category: "Romance",
      question: "Which movie features Aamir Khan and Kajol in the lead roles, where they fall in love despite their differences?",
      options: [
        "Tujhe Meri Kasam",
        "Dilwale Dulhania Le Jayenge",
        "Fanaa",
        "Hum Dil De Chuke Sanam"
      ],
      answer: "Fanaa"
    },
    {
      category: "Romance",
      question: "Which romantic movie features Deepika Padukone and Ranbir Kapoor in the lead roles?",
      options: [
        "Yeh Jawaani Hai Deewani",
        "Ae Dil Hai Mushkil",
        "Kabhi Khushi Kabhie Gham",
        "Barfi!"
      ],
      answer: "Yeh Jawaani Hai Deewani"
    },
    {
      category: "Romance",
      question: "Which movie revolves around a love story between a student and a teacher played by Hrithik Roshan and Aishwarya Rai?",
      options: [
        "Jodhaa Akbar",
        "Taal",
        "Guzaarish",
        "Mohenjo Daro"
      ],
      answer: "Guzaarish"
    },
    {
      category: "Thriller",
      question: "In which movie does Hrithik Roshan play a mastermind criminal in a thrilling heist?",
      options: [
        "Dhoom 2",
        "Bang Bang!",
        "War",
        "Krrish"
      ],
      answer: "Dhoom 2"
    },
    {
      category: "Thriller",
      question: "Which film features a psychological thriller about a woman who is trapped in her own home?",
      options: [
        "Kahaani",
        "Talaash",
        "Drishyam",
        "The Shining"
      ],
      answer: "Kahaani"
    },
    {
      category: "Thriller",
      question: "In which movie does Salman Khan play a character in pursuit of a serial killer?",
      options: [
        "Race 3",
        "Wanted",
        "Bajrangi Bhaijaan",
        "Dabangg"
      ],
      answer: "Race 3"
    },
    {
      category: "Thriller",
      question: "Which movie involves a young man who seeks revenge after being framed for a crime he did not commit?",
      options: [
        "Drishyam",
        "Talaash",
        "Sultan",
        "Murder 2"
      ],
      answer: "Drishyam"
    },
    {
      question: "Which fuel type is commonly used in cars?",
      options: ["Diesel", "Electricity", "Gasoline", "All of the above"],
      answer: "All of the above",
      category: "Cars"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the typical seating capacity of a sedan car?",
      options: ["2", "4-5", "6-8", "10+"],
      answer: "4-5",
      category: "Cars"
    },
    {
      question: "Which of these features is commonly found in modern cars?",
      options: ["Autonomous Driving", "Solar Panels", "Horse Saddle", "Steam Engine"],
      answer: "Autonomous Driving",
      category: "Cars"
    },
    {
      question: "Which country is known for producing luxury cars like BMW and Mercedes-Benz?",
      options: ["Japan", "USA", "Germany", "Italy"],
      answer: "Germany",
      category: "Cars"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the primary purpose of trucks?",
      options: ["Carrying passengers", "Transporting goods", "Racing", "Towing boats"],
      answer: "Transporting goods",
      category: "Trucks"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the term for a truck with a detachable trailer?",
      options: ["Flatbed Truck", "Semi-Truck", "Dump Truck", "Box Truck"],
      answer: "Semi-Truck",
      category: "Trucks"
    },
    {
      question: "Which type of truck is used in construction for moving materials like sand and gravel?",
      options: ["Dump Truck", "Box Truck", "Tow Truck", "Ice Cream Truck"],
      answer: "Dump Truck",
      category: "Trucks"
    },
    {
      question: "Which fuel is most commonly used in large trucks?",
      options: ["Gasoline", "Electricity", "Diesel", "Hydrogen"],
      answer: "Diesel",
      category: "Trucks"
    },
    {
      question: "Which type of train runs on electricity?",
      options: ["Steam Train", "Diesel Train", "Electric Train", "Maglev Train"],
      answer: "Electric Train",
      category: "Trains"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the term for a high-speed train that uses magnetic levitation?",
      options: ["Bullet Train", "Maglev Train", "Freight Train", "Subway Train"],
      answer: "Maglev Train",
      category: "Trains"
    },
    {
      question: "Which type of train is used for carrying goods?",
      options: ["Passenger Train", "Freight Train", "Bullet Train", "Commuter Train"],
      answer: "Freight Train",
      category: "Trains"
    },
    {
      question: "What do trains typically run on?",
      options: ["Rubber Tires", "Tracks", "Dirt Roads", "None of the above"],
      answer: "Tracks",
      category: "Trains"
    },
    {
      question: "What powers a bicycle?",
      options: ["Electric Motor", "Gasoline", "Human Effort", "Solar Energy"],
      answer: "Human Effort",
      category: "Bicycles"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the primary safety gear for a cyclist?",
      options: ["Helmet", "Gloves", "Knee Pads", "Sunglasses"],
      answer: "Helmet",
      category: "Bicycles"
    },
    {
      question: "Which type of bicycle is designed for off-road cycling?",
      options: ["Road Bike", "Mountain Bike", "Hybrid Bike", "BMX Bike"],
      answer: "Mountain Bike",
      category: "Bicycles"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the common number of wheels on a standard bicycle?",
      options: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
      answer: "2",
      category: "Bicycles"
    },
    {
      question: "Which type of ship is used for carrying goods across oceans?",
      options: ["Cargo Ship", "Fishing Boat", "Speedboat", "Yacht"],
      answer: "Cargo Ship",
      category: "Ships and Boats"
    },
    {
      question: "Which of these is a small boat used for recreation?",
      options: ["Yacht", "Canoe", "Cruise Ship", "Submarine"],
      answer: "Canoe",
      category: "Ships and Boats"
    },
    {
      question: "Which type of ship is used for passenger travel across oceans?",
      options: ["Cargo Ship", "Fishing Boat", "Cruise Ship", "Tugboat"],
      answer: "Cruise Ship",
      category: "Ships and Boats"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the primary purpose of a fishing boat?",
      options: ["Transporting goods", "Recreation", "Catching fish", "Military defense"],
      answer: "Catching fish",
      category: "Ships and Boats"
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is a prominent Indian classical instrument used in both Hindustani and Carnatic music?",
      options: ["Sitar", "Tabla", "Veena", "Flute"],
      answer: "Tabla",
      category: "Indian Classical Music"
    },
    {
      question: "What are the two major traditions of Indian classical music?",
      options: ["Hindustani and Carnatic", "Hindustani and Western", "Carnatic and Folk", "Folk and Classical"],
      answer: "Hindustani and Carnatic",
      category: "Indian Classical Music"
    },
    {
      question: "Who is regarded as the 'Father of Indian Classical Music'?",
      options: ["Tansen", "Bhimsen Joshi", "Ravi Shankar", "Ustad Zakir Hussain"],
      answer: "Tansen",
      category: "Classical Music"
    },
    {
      question: "Which raga is traditionally performed during the morning hours in Indian classical music?",
      options: ["Raga Yaman", "Raga Bhairav", "Raga Hamsadhwani", "Raga Bhairavi"],
      answer: "Raga Bhairav",
      category: "Classical Music"
    },
    {
      question: "Which folk music form is famous in the state of Punjab and is characterized by energetic dance movements?",
      options: ["Garba", "Bhangra", "Lavani", "Ghoomar"],
      answer: "Bhangra",
      category: "Folk Music"
    },
    {
      question: "Which musical instrument is commonly associated with Indian folk music, especially in Rajasthan?",
      options: ["Sitar", "Dholak", "Sarangi", "Tanpura"],
      answer: "Sarangi",
      category: "Indian Folk Music"
    },
    {
      question: "Which Indian state is known for its traditional folk dance form 'Garba', often performed during the Navratri festival?",
      options: ["Maharashtra", "Gujarat", "Punjab", "Karnataka"],
      answer: "Gujarat",
      category: "Folk Music"
    },
    {
      question: "Which folk music genre, originating from Tamil Nadu, is known for its devotional songs and was popularized by singers like T.M. Soundararajan?",
      options: ["Baul", "Kaili", "Carnatic", "Gana"],
      answer: "Carnatic",
      category: "Indian Folk Music"
    },
    {
      question: "Who is considered one of the pioneers of Indian rap music, known for his hit song 'Meri Indian Rap'?",
      options: ["Divine", "Yo Yo Honey Singh", "Brodha V", "Bohemia"],
      answer: "Bohemia",
      category: "Rap"
    },
    {
      question: "Which Indian rapper is famous for his breakthrough song 'Meri Gully Mein'?",
      options: ["Emiway Bantai", "Divine", "Badshah", "Raftaar"],
      answer: "Divine",
      category: "Rap"
    },
    {
      question: "Which Indian rapper's debut album 'Desi Hip-Hop' gained massive popularity in the hip-hop scene?",
      options: ["Yo Yo Honey Singh", "Brodha V", "Raftaar", "Bohemia"],
      answer: "Yo Yo Honey Singh",
      category: "Rap"
    },
    {
      question: "Which city is considered the birthplace of Indian rap, particularly known for the rise of artists like Divine and Naezy?",
      options: ["Delhi", "Mumbai", "Kolkata", "Bangalore"],
      answer: "Mumbai",
      category: "Rap"
    },
    {
      question: "Which Sufi singer is famously known for popularizing the qawwali genre with songs like 'Tajdar-e-Haram'?",
      options: ["Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan", "Abida Parveen", "Rahat Fateh Ali Khan", "Mehdi Hassan"],
      answer: "Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan",
      category: "Sufi Music"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the primary theme of Sufi music?",
      options: ["Love and devotion", "Revolutionary ideas", "Romanticism", "Nature's beauty"],
      answer: "Love and devotion",
      category: "Sufi Music"
    },
    {
      question: "Which form of Sufi music is a devotional genre performed in a group setting, featuring energetic chanting and rhythmic clapping?",
      options: ["Qawwali", "Ghazal", "Kaili", "Dastan"],
      answer: "Qawwali",
      category: "Sufi Music"
    },
    {
      question: "Which poet and philosopher, considered one of the greatest Sufi saints, is known for his works in Persian and his spiritual teachings?",
      options: ["Rumi", "Shams Tabrizi", "Iqbal", "Khwaja Moinuddin Chishti"],
      answer: "Rumi",
      category: "Sufi Music"
    },
    {
      question: "Which string instrument is often associated with Indian classical music and features a resonating gourd?",
      options: ["Sitar", "Violin", "Guitar", "Veena"],
      answer: "Sitar",
      category: "Instrumental Music"
    },
    {
      question: "Which instrument, commonly used in orchestras, produces sound by pressing keys to allow air to flow through its pipes?",
      options: ["Organ", "Flute", "Oboe", "Clarinet"],
      answer: "Organ",
      category: "Instrumental Music"
    },
    {
      question: "Which percussion instrument consists of tuned metal bars arranged like a keyboard and is played with mallets?",
      options: ["Marimba", "Xylophone", "Glockenspiel", "Vibraphone"],
      answer: "Glockenspiel",
      category: "Instrumental Music"
    },
    {
      question: "Which instrument, known for its deep and resonant sound, is the largest member of the brass family?",
      options: ["Tuba", "Trombone", "French Horn", "Euphonium"],
      answer: "Tuba",
      category: "Instrumental Music"
    },
    {
      question: "Which political system is characterized by a single party controlling the government, and no opposition parties are allowed?",
      options: ["Democracy", "Oligarchy", "Communism", "Dictatorship"],
      answer: "Communism",
      category: "Political Systems"
    },
    {
      question: "In a parliamentary democracy, who is typically the head of government?",
      options: ["President", "Prime Minister", "King", "Chancellor"],
      answer: "Prime Minister",
      category: "Political Systems"
    },
    {
      question: "Which system of government divides power between a central government and regional governments?",
      options: ["Federalism", "Unitary System", "Confederation", "Absolute Monarchy"],
      answer: "Federalism",
      category: "Political Systems"
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following countries has a system of government where the monarch's powers are limited by a constitution?",
      options: ["United Kingdom", "Saudi Arabia", "North Korea", "China"],
      answer: "United Kingdom",
      category: "Political Systems"
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the current Prime Minister of India?",
      options: ["Narendra Modi", "Rahul Gandhi", "Manmohan Singh", "Atal Bihari Vajpayee"],
      answer: "Narendra Modi",
      category: "Indian Politics"
    },
    {
      question: "Which article of the Indian Constitution deals with the Fundamental Rights?",
      options: ["Article 21", "Article 370", "Article 19", "Article 14"],
      answer: "Article 21",
      category: "Indian Politics"
    },
    {
      question: "Which political party was founded by Dr. B.R. Ambedkar and is known for advocating the rights of Dalits?",
      options: ["Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP)", "Indian National Congress (INC)", "Bahujan Samaj Party (BSP)", "Communist Party of India (CPI)"],
      answer: "Bahujan Samaj Party (BSP)",
      category: "Indian Politics"
    },
    {
      question: "In which year did India gain independence from British rule?",
      options: ["1942", "1947", "1950", "1960"],
      answer: "1947",
      category: "Indian Politics"
    },
    {
      question: "Which country is known for having the longest continuous democracy?",
      options: ["United States", "United Kingdom", "India", "Switzerland"],
      answer: "United Kingdom",
      category: "World Politics"
    },
    {
      question: "Who was the first female Chancellor of Germany?",
      options: ["Margaret Thatcher", "Angela Merkel", "Golda Meir", "Jacinda Ardern"],
      answer: "Angela Merkel",
      category: "World Politics"
    },
    {
      question: "Which international organization was established to promote peace and cooperation after World War II?",
      options: ["United Nations", "World Trade Organization", "European Union", "International Monetary Fund"],
      answer: "United Nations",
      category: "World Politics"
    },
    {
      question: "Which country became independent from the Soviet Union in 1991 and has since become a major player in global politics?",
      options: ["Ukraine", "Georgia", "Estonia", "Russia"],
      answer: "Russia",
      category: "World Politics"
    },
    {
      question: "Who is considered the Supreme God in Hindu mythology, often depicted as the creator, preserver, and destroyer of the universe?",
      options: ["Brahma", "Vishnu", "Shiva", "Indra"],
      answer: "Vishnu",
      category: "Indian mythology"
    },
    {
      question: "Which demon king was defeated by Lord Rama in the epic Ramayana?",
      options: ["Ravana", "Kumbhakarna", "Vibhishana", "Hiranyakashipu"],
      answer: "Ravana",
      category: "Indian mythology"
    },
    {
      question: "In the Mahabharata, who is the mother of the Pandavas?",
      options: ["Kunti", "Draupadi", "Satyavati", "Gandhari"],
      answer: "Kunti",
      category: "Indian mythology"
    },
    {
      question: "Which goddess is often depicted riding a tiger or lion and is associated with strength, war, and protection?",
      options: ["Saraswati", "Lakshmi", "Durga", "Parvati"],
      answer: "Durga",
      category: "Indian mythology"
    },
    {
      question: "Who is considered the king of the Greek gods and the ruler of Mount Olympus?",
      options: ["Apollo", "Zeus", "Poseidon", "Hades"],
      answer: "Zeus",
      category: "Greek Mythology"
    },
    {
      question: "Which Greek hero is known for his twelve labors, including slaying the Nemean Lion?",
      options: ["Perseus", "Theseus", "Heracles", "Achilles"],
      answer: "Heracles",
      category: "Greek Mythology"
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the Greek goddess of wisdom, courage, and warfare?",
      options: ["Hera", "Athena", "Artemis", "Aphrodite"],
      answer: "Athena",
      category: "Greek Mythology"
    },
    {
      question: "Which Greek god is the ruler of the underworld?",
      options: ["Zeus", "Apollo", "Hades", "Hermes"],
      answer: "Hades",
      category: "Greek Mythology"
    },
    {
      question: "Who is considered the king of the gods and ruler of the sky in Egyptian mythology?",
      options: ["Ra", "Osiris", "Horus", "Amun"],
      answer: "Ra",
      category: "Egyptian Mythology"
    },
    {
      question: "Which goddess is known as the protector of the dead and the wife of Osiris?",
      options: ["Isis", "Nephthys", "Bastet", "Sekhmet"],
      answer: "Isis",
      category: "Egyptian Mythology"
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the Egyptian god of the underworld and judge of the dead?",
      options: ["Horus", "Anubis", "Thoth", "Osiris"],
      answer: "Osiris",
      category: "Egyptian Mythology"
    },
    {
      question: "Which goddess, depicted as a lioness, is associated with war and healing?",
      options: ["Sekhmet", "Bastet", "Hathor", "Tefnut"],
      answer: "Sekhmet",
      category: "Egyptian Mythology"
    },
    {
      question: "Who is considered the king of the Roman gods and ruler of the sky?",
      options: ["Jupiter", "Neptune", "Mars", "Apollo"],
      answer: "Jupiter",
      category: "Roman Mythology"
    },
    {
      question: "Which Roman goddess is associated with love, beauty, and fertility?",
      options: ["Venus", "Minerva", "Diana", "Ceres"],
      answer: "Venus",
      category: "Roman Mythology"
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the Roman god of war, often depicted as a warrior in battle armor?",
      options: ["Mars", "Juno", "Vulcan", "Saturn"],
      answer: "Mars",
      category: "Roman Mythology"
    },
    {
      question: "Which Roman god is known as the messenger of the gods and the god of commerce and travel?",
      options: ["Mercury", "Apollo", "Bacchus", "Pluto"],
      answer: "Mercury",
      category: "Roman Mythology"
    },
    {
      question: "Which Free Fire character is known for her healing ability and is often referred to as the 'angel of battle'?",
      options: ["A124", "Shirou", "Moco", "Paloma"],
      answer: "A124",
      category: "Free Fire"
    },
    {
      question: "Which weapon in Free Fire is famous for its long-range sniper abilities?",
      options: ["AK47", "AWM", "M4A1", "MP40"],
      answer: "AWM",
      category: "Free Fire"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the maximum number of players in a Free Fire squad?",
      options: ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
      answer: "4",
      category: "Free Fire"
    },
    {
      question: "Which Free Fire character has the ability to increase the speed of throwing grenades?",
      options: ["Wukong", "Dasha", "Hayato", "Skyler"],
      answer: "Dasha",
      category: "Free Fire"
    },
    {
      question: "Which BGMI vehicle is known for its speed and ability to cross rough terrains?",
      options: ["Dacia", "Buggy", "UAZ", "Motorcycle"],
      answer: "Buggy",
      category: "BGMI"
    },
    {
      question: "Which BGMI weapon is the most powerful sniper rifle with the highest damage?",
      options: ["M416", "AWM", "Kar98k", "SKS"],
      answer: "AWM",
      category: "BGMI"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the maximum number of players in a BGMI squad?",
      options: ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
      answer: "4",
      category: "BGMI"
    },
    {
      question: "In BGMI, which item is used to heal players over time?",
      options: ["First Aid Kit", "Bandage", "Med Kit", "Painkiller"],
      answer: "Painkiller",
      category: "BGMI"
    },
    {
      question: "Which COD game introduced the popular Zombies mode?",
      options: ["Call of Duty: Modern Warfare", "Call of Duty: Black Ops", "Call of Duty: Advanced Warfare", "Call of Duty: World at War"],
      answer: "Call of Duty: World at War",
      category: "COD"
    },
    {
      question: "Which COD weapon is known for its high damage and rate of fire, and is a favorite in multiplayer modes?",
      options: ["AK-47", "M4A1", "MP5", "RPD"],
      answer: "MP5",
      category: "COD"
    },
    {
      question: "In Call of Duty: Warzone, what is the maximum number of players in a single battle royale match?",
      options: ["50", "100", "150", "200"],
      answer: "150",
      category: "COD"
    },
    {
      question: "Which COD character is famous for saying 'The price is right' in the campaign mode?",
      options: ["Soap MacTavish", "Captain Price", "Alex Mason", "Ghost"],
      answer: "Captain Price",
      category: "COD"
    },
    {
      question: "Which city is the setting for the original Grand Theft Auto (GTA) game?",
      options: ["Vice City", "Liberty City", "San Andreas", "London"],
      answer: "Liberty City",
      category: "GTA"
    },
    {
      question: "In which GTA game did the character 'CJ' (Carl Johnson) appear?",
      options: ["GTA IV", "GTA V", "GTA San Andreas", "GTA Vice City"],
      answer: "GTA San Andreas",
      category: "GTA"
    },
    {
      question: "Which vehicle is commonly associated with the GTA series and is known for its muscle car appearance?",
      options: ["Comet", "Banshee", "Infernus", "Sultan"],
      answer: "Infernus",
      category: "GTA"
    },
    {
      question: "In Grand Theft Auto V, which of the following is NOT one of the three playable characters?",
      options: ["Michael De Santa", "Trevor Philips", "Franklin Clinton", "Tommy Vercetti"],
      answer: "Tommy Vercetti",
      category: "GTA"
    },
    {
      question: "What does IPO stand for in the context of finance?",
      options: ["International Public Offering", "Initial Public Offering", "Initial Private Offering", "Investor's Public Offering"],
      answer: "Initial Public Offering",
      category: "IPO"
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is a reason a company might choose to go public with an IPO?",
      options: ["To raise capital for expansion", "To increase control over the company", "To avoid paying taxes", "To keep the company private"],
      answer: "To raise capital for expansion",
      category: "IPO"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the primary purpose of an underwriter in an IPO?",
      options: ["To invest in the company", "To help price and sell the shares", "To manage the company's finances", "To ensure the company's legal compliance"],
      answer: "To help price and sell the shares",
      category: "IPO"
    },
    {
      question: "What is a common risk for investors during an IPO?",
      options: ["The stock price can fall significantly after the offering", "The company may stop paying dividends immediately", "The company is required to distribute earnings", "The IPO process always guarantees a profit"],
      answer: "The stock price can fall significantly after the offering",
      category: "IPO"
    },
    {
      question: "What is a stock?",
      options: ["A type of bond", "A share of ownership in a company", "A government investment tool", "A loan issued to companies"],
      answer: "A share of ownership in a company",
      category: "Basics Stock Markett"
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is an example of a stock exchange?",
      options: ["NASDAQ", "S&P 500", "Futures Market", "T-bill Market"],
      answer: "NASDAQ",
      category: "Basics Stock Market"
    },
    {
      question: "What is a dividend?",
      options: ["The price of a stock", "The interest paid on stocks", "A payment made to stockholders from company profits", "The cost of buying a stock"],
      answer: "A payment made to stockholders from company profits",
      category: "Basics Stock Market"
    },
    {
      question: "What does it mean when a stock is said to be 'bullish'?",
      options: ["The stock price is expected to decline", "The stock price is expected to rise", "The stock has high volatility", "The stock has a dividend yield"],
      answer: "The stock price is expected to rise",
      category: "Basics Stock Market"
    },
    {
      question: "What does 'IPO' stand for in the stock market?",
      options: ["Initial Private Offering", "International Public Offering", "Initial Public Offering", "Investor's Public Option"],
      answer: "Initial Public Offering",
      category: "Stock Market Terms"
    },
    {
      question: "What is a 'bull market'?",
      options: ["A market where prices are falling", "A market where prices are stable", "A market where prices are rising", "A market with low trading volume"],
      answer: "A market where prices are rising",
      category: "Stock Market Terms"
    },
    {
      question: "What is a 'bear market'?",
      options: ["A market where prices are rising", "A market where prices are falling", "A market with high investor sentiment", "A market driven by speculation"],
      answer: "A market where prices are falling",
      category: "Stock Market Terms"
    },
    {
      question: "What does 'dividend yield' refer to?",
      options: ["The growth rate of a stock", "The income generated from stock investment expressed as a percentage of the stock price", "The total value of dividends paid per year", "The total market capitalization of a company"],
      answer: "The income generated from stock investment expressed as a percentage of the stock price",
      category: "Stock Market Terms"
    },

    {
      question: "Which of the following is the largest stock exchange in the world by market capitalization?",
      options: ["London Stock Exchange", "NASDAQ", "Tokyo Stock Exchange", "New York Stock Exchange"],
      answer: "New York Stock Exchange",
      category: "Global Stock Markets"
    },
    {
      question: "Which country has the Tokyo Stock Exchange as its major stock exchange?",
      options: ["China", "India", "Japan", "South Korea"],
      answer: "Japan",
      category: "Global Stock Markets"
    },
    {
      question: "Which global stock index represents the stock performance of the top 500 companies in the United States?",
      options: ["DAX", "Nikkei 225", "S&P 500", "FTSE 100"],
      answer: "S&P 500",
      category: "Global Stock Markets"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of the stock exchange located in Hong Kong?",
      options: ["Hong Kong Stock Exchange", "Shanghai Stock Exchange", "Shenzhen Stock Exchange", "Taiwan Stock Exchange"],
      answer: "Hong Kong Stock Exchange",
      category: "Global Stock Markets"
    }
  ];

export { Feild}